milandirect.com.au 2016-06-25

# Privacy Policy

www.milandirect.com.au, www.milandirect.co.uk and www.mdfinishings.com.au referred to below as Milan Direct, is an online retailer of consumer goods.

At Milan Direct, we value our relationship with you and the other users of this website. We recognize that you may be concerned about our collection, use, and disclosure of your personally identifiable information that we may collect when you use the Web Site. Accordingly, we have implemented this Privacy Policy to inform you of the information that we collect from you, how we collect this information, and what we do with it after we collect it. If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: sales@milandirect.com.au

**Milan Direct’s Commitment to Online Security**

At Milan Direct, your personal information is treated with the greatest of care. Sensitive payment information such as credit card details is NEVER stored on the Internet with our system. Once you type your information, it is sent instantly, encrypted, direct to our order processing system. We employ the latest 1024-bit encryption technology in all areas of the site which require you to provide payment information. This is done to protect you from unauthorized use of the information you are sending to our server. This website is registered with site identification authorities to enable your browser to confirm our security identity before any transmission is sent. With this technology, the identity of this site is automatically confirmed behind the scenes prior to the transmission of any sensitive information requested to complete an online order. This also ensures that your data reaches your intended target or your browser notifies you that the potential receiving site looks suspicious and should be avoided.

Physical, electronic and managerial procedures have been employed to safeguard the security and integrity of personal information. The Milan Direct website encrypts sensitive information wherever Milan Direct requests it.

**Email Newsletter Subscription**

All our newsletters contain a link to unsubscribe. You will not receive newsletters from us again if you choose to unsubscribe. In order to make our emails more relevant and useful to you, our servers may receive a confirmation when you open email from us.

**Being Included In and Removed From Our Email Newsletters**

You will be included in our email newsletter mailing list (which include special offers, competitions, new product arrival alerts and other communication related to our services or the products we offer) if you subscribe to our newsletter or if you make a purchase from us or have requested that we notify you of an items expected arrival and we expect to receive other items that are similar or complimentary. Every newsletter we send has an unsubscribe option in the newsletter. This will always be clear and easy to locate. You may unsubscribe from any mailing list whenever you wish and you will be immediately removed as per your request. You also have the option of emailing unsubscribe@milandirect.com.au and a member of our Customer Service Team will unsubscribe you if you provide them with the email address that is subscribed.

**Personal Information that Milan Direct May Collect Online**

Milan Direct collects personal information online, including names, postal and e-mail addresses, phone numbers and billing information.

**How Milan Direct Uses Personal Information Collected Online**

We will use your personal information only for the purpose of processing your order and to communicate effectively with you. This communication includes but is not limited to; emailing you tax invoices, dispatch and tracking information, returns and exchange authorisations, etc. As a condition of sale we reserve the right to email you special offer promotions that we believe will be of interest to you. You may, once you have placed your order, advise us that you are not interested in these offers and we will consequently not send these to you. To do this, please send this request to unsubscribe@milandirect.com.au.com.au. In any event, you may, at any time, unsubscribe from any special offer promotions we send you, and your unsubscribe request will be actioned immediately.

**How Your Information May Be Shared**

We never sell or rent your personal information. Milan Direct may release personal information under the following circumstances:

  * Where release is required by law (for example, a subpoena) or regulation or is requested by a government agency;
  * Where our records indicate a company or an individual may be engaged in fraudulent activity or other deceptive practices that a governmental agency should be made aware of;
  * To appropriate persons, where your communication suggests possible harm to others

**Computer Tracking and Cookies**

This website is not set up to track, collect or distribute personal information not entered by visitors. Our site logs do generate certain kinds of non-identifying site usage data, such as the number of hits and visits to our sites. This information is used for internal purposes by technical support staff to provide better services to the public and may also be provided to others, but again, the statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information.

**Changes to this Privacy Notice, Conditions of Use and Notices**

This Privacy Notice and our Terms of Use may change over time and the use of information which we gather now is subject to these Notices and Terms as modified. If you visit our Web site, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Legal Notices, including the application of the laws of the State of Victoria, Australia.
